Hello, I'm Park Jin-beom, who is working on visual creative in the name of TAGIREN.
Recently, I worked on a girl group aespa's We Flash album i-aespa character artwork.
Hi, I'm Yon Sanchez, a digital fashion creator and 3D artist.
My work focuses on creating realistic and visual-friendly clothes.
I worked with Jin-beom on the We Flash Universe project.
Two years ago, while preparing for an online lecture,
I wanted to explain to the students how to make clothes and how to use existing asset clothes.
At that time, I was looking for assets to use.
At that time, Yon had a lot of professionally and systematically produced clothes,
so based on Yon's clothes,
I wanted to explain how to customize them to the students.
That's when I got in touch with Yon.
I think that's when we became friends.
I looked at Jin-beom's Instagram and thought,
Okay, this person knows what she's doing.
I love her style.
I want to work with her.
I-aespa's character artwork was uploaded to my SNS on SM Entertainment.
I saw the previous character artwork and thankfully, he contacted me about the artwork.
I think it was really good at the time.
I always tried to recreate the style I had been looking for.
I gave him a good chance to redesign the character and design the outfit.
I had a lot of fun working on it and it was a meaningful project.
At that time, I was in touch with Yon.
I know Yon's excellent skills,
so I asked him to work with me on the outfit for I-aespa.
Jin-beom sent me a direct message asking me about this collaboration.
Without thinking too much, I said,
Let's go ahead with it.
We connected very quickly.
It was very natural.
It can't be better than this.
Collaborating together has been very fluid.
We actively share connections,
we give mutual feedback and we help each other a lot.
The project had a clear line from the beginning.
The process was very fluid.
I quickly made the basic structure and then added the details.
Yon and I had worked on a collaboration several times before,
and thanks to this project,
we were able to quickly proceed with the project with smooth communication.
Thanks to the collaboration between Clou and Marvellous Designer,
I think we can work faster and more easily.
Especially using Marvellous Designer,
we can spend more time on concepts and level of detail,
so we were able to create a high-quality artwork.
We were also able to work more effectively and efficiently
because we collaborate and communicate using Clou and Marvellous Designer.
And since the files are compatible,
it's much easier to review them.
I have been working with other K-pop artists since IESPA's Reflash Universe project.
I want to have a career in the game industry as well as fashion or entertainment,
but my ultimate goal is to become a 3D artist in various industries,
especially as a 3D character artist.
I loved working on the IESPA project.
It opened many doors for me to different projects with fashion brands,
the automotive industry, and projects where you can always learn something new.
As a dream, I would like to create my own fashion brand.
But it's a long-term dream, so I'm not in a hurry to do it.
I need to keep learning, exploring, meeting people,
and keeping myself informed about trends.
Clou is an essential part of my work.
I would say it's my daily life.
Thanks to this, I can experiment digitally with different forms.
I hope to show you my new projects.
Right now, I'm mainly dealing with Marvellous Designer,
and I know that the compatibility between Clou and Marvellous Designer software
is really good.
For my目標 and the goal I set,
it's a tool a Marvellous Designer needs to be able to achieve,
so I'm going to keep using it for my career.
I'm planning to keep it up.
Coming Q1 2017
Q2 2017
Q3 2017
Q4 2017
Q5 2017
Q7 2017
Q8 2016
Q9 2017
Q11 2017
Q12 2017
Q13 2017
Q13 2020
Q14 2020
Q15 2020
Q16 2020
Q14 2020
Q15 2020
Q15 2021